ADIS SKENDER

Zenica, Crkvice · 062-251-859 Email: adis.skender2018@size.ba GitHub: github.com/adisskender01

My name is Adis Skender and I am 25 years old. I have successfully graduated at Polytechnic Faculty in Zenica and earned bachelor's degree in Software engineering. I consider myself exceptionally enthusiastic and passionate about learning new technologies and expanding my knowledge especially in terms of Web development and Frontend. In terms of programming languages, I have an average experience in C#, specifically .NET Core for the backend which I used to create APIs to establish connection between backend and frontend, as well as storing data inside of the database. On the frontend side I have used HTML, CSS, JavaScript as well as React library for building various projects and all of the completed ones can be found on my GitHub account. I had opportunity to work on plenty E-commerce projects as an Intern using Shopware 6 platform and JTL Wawi, highlighting Homepages, product pages, various categories for Web Shops, etc. As for managing database I have previous experience working with SQL Server and I am open for expanding my knowledge further in this realm.

EXPERIENCE

APRIL 2021 - MAY 2021

INTERNSHIP, SOFTRAY SOLUTIONS

Studied and worked with lots of technologies such as C#, .NET Core, Angular framework and SQL Server to create functional and reliable "To do" app.

DECEMBER 2023 – MARCH 2024 INTERNSHIP, COMMERCE CARE

Worked on numerous e-commerce projects in staging phase, creating and managing Web Shops utilizing Shopware 6 platform

EDUCATION

SEPTEMBER 2014 - MAY 2018

GRADUATE, TECHNICAL HIGH SCHOOL

I graduated at Technical High School in Zenica with highest GPA

OCTOBER 2018 – JUNE 2023

GRADUATE, POLYTECHNIC FACULTY

Bachelor's degree in software engineering

SKILLS

- Planning
- Troubleshooting

- Web development
- Problem solving

ACTIVITIES

Received a certificate for successful participation on Internship program led by company Softray Solutions